#### **JORGE SARRICOLEA VEYRO**

Full-Stack developer with more than 2 years of experience. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends.













#### **About me**

+2 years ago, I embarked on my journey in web development, creating attractive and functional web applications. My focus is on merging technical skills with a keen eye for design, which drives me to constantly advance. I firmly believe that true changes requires order, discipline, and perseverance, which are essential for achieving success.

### **Experience**

### **Full-Stack Developer**

Sweet fit | April 2024 - May 2024

I developed a custom administrative platform from scratch for Sweet Fit restaurant, facilitating coupon management and allocation to attract new customers. I led back-end development in JavaScript and collaborated with a team for the front-end development.

# **Django Developer**

Seguros Gutierrez y Arredondo | April 2024 - May 2024

I developed a data retrieval form using Django and PostgreSQL to streamline the prospect acquisition process and enhance efficiency for the recruitment team. Focus was on seamlessly capturing and storing prospect data to optimize lead management.

# **Full-Stack Developer**

ICCBR 2024 | January 2024 - March 2024

I collaborated in a team to refactor the entire platform, transitioning from PHP to Astro + JavaScript to remove vulnerabilities. My primary focus included building a robust RESTful API for payment processing and email notifications for ticket purchases. Additionally, I contributed to frontend improvements by refactoring and creating UI components.

# **Bubble Developer**

Datamatic Software | June 2022 - July 2022

I was tasked with specific responsibilities across various projects. This included bug fixing, enhancing user interfaces, improving back-end workflows, and updating APIs consumed by each project.

C

### **Bubble Developer**

#### Jumwork | June 2018 - Janurary 2022

I worked on developing the platform from scratch. This platform is a marketplace with an integrated chat, auction system, email notifications, and a payment gateway via Stripe. My primary goal was to work on all modules to deliver a functional, responsive platform without any development errors.

#### **Education**

#### Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida | 2020 - 2024

Computer Stystems Engineer

### **Projects**

#### THE MOVIES APP

### ☑ ○ JOORGE SEARCH

**公** ()

The Movies APP is a platform designed to view information about the most popular, highest-rated, and upcoming movies. The information is obtained from TheMovieDB API.

This is a small search engine with simulated Google-like recommendations, the intention is to demonstrate my UI skills.

#### **WEATHER APP**

**ぱの** 

## ROCK, PAPER OR SCISSORS 2 0

When working with REST APIs, the ideal project to practice is to make a weather app. I have used the free OpenWeatherMap API. The design is minimalist, and I have

used the icons that this API contains.

The famous Rock, Paper, Scissors game, play against the computer and win?...

Designed to be responsive and simple.

#### **RECIPIES NET**

**6** 0

#### **CALORIE CALCULATOR**

This is a recipe search engine obtained through the MealDB API. It features an attractive and responsive user interface that allows users to search for a wide variety of culinary recipes. This is a calorie intake calculator designed to help users determine their daily caloric needs based on their level of physical activity. It features a user-friendly and responsive design that makes it easy for individuals to calculate their ideal caloric intake.

# **Main Stack**



# **Skills**

